when I've been building applications with large
当我在构建大型应用程序时
language models
语言模型
I don't think I've ever
我想我从来没有
come to the prompt that I ended up using in the final
来到我最后在期末考试中使用的提示符
application on my first attempt
我第一次尝试就申请了
and this isn't what matters
这并不重要
as long as you have a good process to
只要你有一个好的过程
interestively make your prompt better
有趣的是，让你的提示更好
then you'll be able to come to something that
然后你就能得到一些
works well for the task you want to achieve
对你想要完成的任务很有效
you may have heard me say that when I
你可能听我说过，当我
trade a machine learning model
交易一个机器学习模型
it almost never works the first time
第一次几乎没有成功过
in fact I'm
事实上，我
very surprised if the first model I train works
如果第一辆I型火车成功了，我很惊讶
I think we're prompting
我想我们是在提示
the odds of it working
成功的几率
the first time is maybe a little bit higher
第一次可能会高一点
but as easy saying
但是很简单
doesn't matter if the first prompt works
第一个提示是否有效并不重要
what matters most of the process
过程中最重要的是什么
for getting two prompts that works for your application
获取适用于您的应用程序的两个提示
so with that let's jump into the code
好了，让我们进入代码
and let me show you some frameworks to think about
让我给你们看一些框架
how to iteratively
如何迭代
develop a prompt
制定一个提示
right
正确的
so if you've taken a machine learning course with me
如果你上过我的机器学习课程
before you may have seen
在你看到之前
me use a diagram
我用一个图表
saying that with machine learning development
随着机器学习的发展
you often have an idea
你经常有想法
and then implement it
然后实现它
so write the code get the data
因此，编写代码获取数据
train your model
训练你的模型
and that gives you an experimental result
这就得到了一个实验结果
and you can then look at that output
然后你可以看看输出
maybe do error analysis
也许可以做错误分析
figure out where it's working or not working
找出它在哪里起作用，在哪里不起作用
and then maybe even change your idea of
然后也许会改变你对
exactly what problem you want to solve or how
确切地说，你想解决什么问题，或者怎么解决
to approach it
接近它
and they change implementation
他们改变了实施方式
and
和
run another experiment and so on and iterate over and
再做一次实验，然后不断重复
over to get to an effective machine learning model
来看看一个有效的机器学习模型
if you're not familiar with machine learning
如果你不熟悉机器学习
and haven't seen
我还没见过
this diagram before
这张图之前
don't worry about it
别担心
not that important for the rest of this presentation
这对接下来的演讲来说并不重要
but when you are writing prompts
但是当你写提示的时候
to develop an application using an Lom
使用Lom开发应用程序
the process can be quite similar
这个过程可能非常相似
where you have an idea for what you want to do
你对自己想做的事情有什么想法
the task you want to complete
你想完成的任务
and you can then
然后你就可以
take a first attempt at writing
第一次尝试写作
a prompt that hopefully is clear and specific
一个提示，希望是明确和具体的
and maybe if appropriate gives the system time to think
如果合适的话，给系统一些思考的时间
and then you can run it and see what result you get
然后你可以运行它，看看得到什么结果
and if it doesn't work well not the first time
如果效果不好，第一次也不行
then the iterative process of
的迭代过程
figuring out why the instructions for example were not
弄清楚为什么指令没有
clear enough
足够清晰
or why it didn't give the album enough time to think
或者为什么它没有给专辑足够的时间去思考
allows you to refine the idea refine the prompt
允许你完善想法完善提示
and so on and to go around this loop multiple times
以此循环多次
until you end up with a prompt that works for your
直到你得到一个适合你的提示
application
应用程序
this too is why I personally have not paid
这也是我个人没有付钱的原因
as much attention
同样多的关注
to the internet articles that say 30 perfect proms
到网上说30个完美舞会的文章
because I think
因为我认为
there probably isn't
可能没有
a perfect prompt for everything under the sun
太阳底下的一切都能得到完美的提示
it's more important than you have a process
这比你有一个流程更重要
for developing a good prompt for your
为您开发一个好的提示
specific application
特定的应用程序
so let's look at an example together in code
让我们一起看一个代码中的例子
I have here
这里有
the starter code that you saw in the previous videos
你在之前的视频中看到的起始代码
have import Openai importos
有进口Openai进口吗
here we get the Openai API key
这里我们得到Openai API密钥
and this is the same helper function that you saw
这和你们看到的辅助函数是一样的
as last time
和上次一样
and
和
I'm going to use as the running example in this video
我将在这个视频中使用它作为运行的例子
the toss of summarizing a fact sheet for a chair
为椅子总结一份情况说明书的折腾
so let me just paste that in here
我把它粘贴在这里
and feel free to pause the video and
可以暂停视频，然后
read this more carefully in the notebook on the left
请仔细阅读左边笔记本上的内容
if you want but here's a factory for a chair
如果你想，这里有个椅子工厂
with a description
有一个描述
saying it's part of a beautiful family of MT
说它是MT美丽大家庭的一部分
century inspired and so on
世纪启发等等
talks about the construction
谈论结构
has the dimensions
有尺寸
options for the chair materials and so on
可选择椅子的材质等
comes from Italy
来自意大利
so let's say you want to take this fat sheet
假设你想要这张厚纸
and help a marketing team write the description
并帮助营销团队撰写产品描述
for a online retail website
一个在线零售网站
let me just quickly
让我快速地讲一下
run these three and then we'll come up with a prompt
运行这三个，然后我们将出现一个提示
as follows and it just
如下，它只是
and it just paces in
然后它就进来了
so my promptpss your task is to help a marketing team
所以我的提示是你的任务是帮助一个营销团队
create
创建
a description for a retail website of the product
该产品零售网站的描述
based on techno fact sheet
基于技术情况说明书
write the project description and so on
写项目描述等等
right so this is my first attempt to
这是我第一次尝试
explain the task to the large language model
向大型语言模型解释任务
so let me hit shift enter
我按shift回车
and this takes a few seconds to run
这需要几秒钟来运行
and we get this result
我们得到了这个结果
it looks like it's done a nice job
看起来它做得不错
writing a description
写描述
introducing a stunning Miss Entry
有请惊艳的入场小姐
Inspire Office Chair
灵感办公椅
Perfect Edition and so on
完美版等等
but when we look at this I go boy this is really long
但是当我们看到这个的时候，我觉得这真的很长
it's done a nice job doing exactly what I asked it to
它完全按照我的要求做得很好
which is start from the technical fact sheet
哪个是从技术说明书开始的
and write a private description
并写一个私人描述
but when I look at as I go
但当我看我走
this is kind of long
这有点长
maybe we wanted to be a little bit shorter
也许我们想要短一点
so I have had an idea
所以我有了一个主意
I wrote a prompt got a result
我写了一个提示得到了一个结果
I'm not that happier of it because it's too long
我不太高兴，因为它太长了
so I will then clarify my prompt
所以我将澄清我的提示
and say
然后说
use
使用
utmost 50 words
50字以内
to try to give better guidance on
试图给出更好的指导
the desired length of this
期望的长度
and this run of the game
这一轮的比赛
okay this actually looks like a
这看起来像a
much nicer short description of the product
对产品的简短描述要好得多
introducing on mid century inspired office chair
介绍一款受世纪中期启发的办公椅
and so on 5 were you just
等等，5是你刚刚
both stylish and practical not bad
既时尚又实用
and let me double check the length that this is
我再检查一下它的长度
so I'm going to take the response
所以我要取这个响应
split it going to where the spaces and then
把它分割到空格，然后
you print out the length
你打印出长度
so it's 52 words actually not bad
所以52个单词其实还不错
large language models are okay
大型语言模型是可以的
but not that great
但也没那么好
at following instructions about a very precise workout
按照指示进行精确的锻炼
but this is actually not bad
但这其实并不坏
sometimes it will print out something with
有时它会打印一些东西
60 or 65 and so on words but it's kind of
60或65之类的词，但它有点
within reason
within reason
some of the things you could try to do would be
你可以尝试做的一些事情是
to say use at most the
说最多使用
three sentences
三句话
let me run that again
我再运行一遍
but these are different ways to tell the large
但这些是不同的方式来告诉大
language model
语言模型
what's the length of the upput that you want
你想要的输出长度是多少
so this is one 2
这是1个2
3 I count three sentences it also did a pretty good job
我数了三个句子，它也做得很好
and then I've also seen people sometimes do things like
我还看到人们有时会做这样的事情
I don't know use that most 280 characters
我不知道，最多用280个字符
large language models because of
大型语言模型是因为
the way they interpret text
他们解读文本的方式
using something called a tokenizer
使用一种叫做标记器的东西
which which I won't talk about
这个我就不说了
but they tend to be so so accounting characters but
但他们往往是会计角色，但是
let's see 281 characters is actually surprising
让我们看看281个字符实际上是令人惊讶的
any close usually a
任何接近的，通常是
large language model doesn't get it quite as close
大型语言模型没有这么接近
but these are different ways
但这是不同的方式
they can play with to try to
他们可以试着玩
control the length of the output
控制输出的长度
that you get but then just
你得到的，但是
switch about to use at most 50 words
切换到最多使用50个单词
and that's our result that we had just now
这就是我们刚刚得到的结果
as we continue to refine this text for our websites
随着我们继续为我们的网站完善这篇文章
we might decide that
我们可能会决定
this website isn't selling
这个网站卖不出去
director consumers is actually intended
导演消费者实际上是有意的
to sell furniture to furniture retailers
向家具零售商出售家具
that would be more interested in the technical
他们会对技术更感兴趣
details of the chair
椅子的细节
and the materials of the chair
还有椅子的材料
in that case you can take this prompt and say
在这种情况下，你可以接受这个提示并说
I want to modify this prompt
我想修改这个提示符
to get it to be more precise
让它更精确
about the technical details
关于技术细节
so let me keep on modifying this prompt
我继续修改这个提示符
and I'm going to say
我要说的是
this description is intended for furniture retailers
本描述适用于家具零售商
so should be technical and focus on materials
所以应该注重技术和材料
products and construct it from
产品和构造
well let's run that
我们运行一下
and let's see
我们来看看
not bad
不坏
says you know cult aluminum base and pneumatic care
说你知道邪教铝制底座和气动护理
high quality materials
优质材料
so by changing the prompt you can get it to
因此，通过更改提示符，您可以将其设置为
focus more on specific characters
更多地关注特定的角色
on specific characteristics you want it to
在你想要的特定特征上
and
和
when I look at this I might decide
当我看到这个的时候，我可能会决定
at the end of the description
在描述的最后
I also wanted to include
我还想包括
the product IDS
产品IDS
so the two offerings of this share SWC110
这两支股票SWC110
Soc 100
Soc 100
so
所以
maybe I can further improve this prompt
也许我可以进一步改进这个提示
and to get it to give me the product IDS
并让它给我产品id
I can add this
我可以加上这个
instruction at the end of the description
说明的最后
include every
包括每一个
7 character product ID in the technical specification
技术规范中的7个字符的产品ID
and
和
let's run it
让我们运行一下
and see what happens
看看会发生什么
and so this is introduced to our missections file
这就是我们的missections文件
office share
办公室分享
shell colours tossel plastic coating aluminum base
外壳颜色抛掷塑料涂层铝基
practical some options
实用的一些选项
talk about the two product IDS
谈谈这两种产品IDS
so this looks pretty good
这看起来很不错
and what you've just seen is a
你刚刚看到的是a
short example of the iterative prompt development
迭代提示开发的简短示例
that many developers will go through
这是许多开发者都会经历的
and I think our guidelines is
我认为我们的指导方针是
in the last video
在上个视频中
you saw user share a number of best practices
您看到用户分享了许多最佳实践
and so what I usually do is
所以我通常做的是
keep best practices like that in mind
记住这样的最佳实践
be clear and specific
要清晰具体
and if necessary give the model time to think
如果有必要，给模型时间思考
with those in mind is worthwhiles often
经常记住这些是值得的
take a first attempt at writing a prompt
第一次尝试写提示
see what happens and then
看看会发生什么
go from there to iteratively refine the prompt
从那里开始迭代地改进提示符
to get closer and closer
越来越近
to the result that you need
得到你想要的结果
and so a lot of the successful prompts that you may see
所以你可能会看到很多成功的提示
using various programs was
使用各种程序
arrive at an iterative process
到达一个迭代过程
like this
像这样
just for fun let me show you an example of
为了好玩，我给你们举个例子
an even more complex
更复杂的是
prompt that might give you a sense of what Chat GPT
提示符，可以让您了解什么是Chat GPT
can do which is I've just added a few
能做的就是我刚刚加了几个
extra instructions here
这里有额外的说明
after the description
在描述之后
include the table that use the product dimensions
包括使用产品尺寸的表
and then you'll format everything as HTML
然后将所有内容格式化为HTML
so let's run that
我们运行一下
and in practice
在实践中
you would end up with a prompt like this
你会得到这样的提示
really only after multiple iterations
实际上只有在多次迭代之后
I don't think I know anyone
我想我谁也不认识
that would write this exact prompt the first time
第一次写的就是这个提示符
they were trying to
他们试图
get the system to process a fact sheet
让系统处理一份情况说明书
and so this actually outputs a bunch of HDML
这实际上输出了一堆HDML
let's display the HDML
让我们显示HDML
to see if this is even valid
看看这是否有效
and I don't actually know what's going to work
我也不知道怎样才能成功
but let's see
但是让我们看看
oh cool alright looks like I rend it
哦，很酷，好吧，看起来我喜欢它
so it has this really nice
它有这个很漂亮
looking description of a chair
看起来像一把椅子
construction materials
建筑材料
product dimensions
产品尺寸
oh it looks like I left out the user
哦，我好像漏掉了用户
most 50 words instructions
最多50个字的说明
so this is a little bit long but if you want that
这个有点长，但是如果你想要的话
you can even feel free to pause the video
你甚至可以随意暂停视频
tell it to be more succinct and
让它更简洁
regenerate this and see what results you get
重新生成它，看看得到什么结果
so I hope you take away from this video
所以我希望你们能从这个视频中受益
that prompt development is an iterative process
快速开发是一个迭代过程
try something
尝试一些
see how it does not yet fulfill exactly what you want
看看它怎么还没有完全满足你想要的
and then think about how to
然后想想怎么
clarify your instructions or in some cases
澄清你的指示，或者在某些情况下
think about how to give it more space to think
想想如何给它更多的思考空间
to get it closer
让它更靠近
to delivering the results that you want
实现你想要的结果
and I think the key to being an
我认为成为一个
effective prompt engineer
有效速递工程师
isn't so much about knowing the perfect prompt
关键不在于知道正确的提示
is about having a good process to develop prompts
是关于有一个好的过程来开发提示吗
that are effective
是有效的
for your application
对于你的申请
and in this video I illustrated
在这个视频中我已经说明了
developing a prompt using just one example
仅使用一个示例开发提示符
for more sophisticated applications
对于更复杂的应用程序
sometimes you will have
有时你会有
multiple examples say a list of 10 or even
很多例子都是10个甚至更多
50 or 100 fat sheets
50或100张胖纸
and iteratively develop a prompt and evaluated
并迭代开发一个提示和评估
against a large set of cases
针对一大堆案件
but for the early development of most applications
但对于大多数应用程序的早期开发
I see many people developing it
我看到很多人都在开发它
sort of the way I am with just one example
就像我举了一个例子一样
but then for more mature applications sometimes
但是对于更成熟的应用程序来说
it could be useful
这可能很有用
to evaluate prompt against a larger set of examples
根据一组更大的例子来评估提示
such as
如
to test different Proms on
来测试不同的舞会
dozens of fact sheets
数十份情况说明书
to see how is average or worst case performances
看看他的平均表现和最差表现
on multiple fact sheets
在多个情况说明书上
but usually you end up doing that
但通常你最后都会这么做
only when an application is more mature
只有当应用程序更成熟时
and you have to have those metrics
你必须有这些指标
to drive that incremental
来推动增量
last few steps of prompt improvement
最后几个步骤的及时改进
so with that
就讲到这里
please do play with the Jupiter code notebook
请使用木星代码笔记本
examples and try out different variations and
并尝试不同的变化和
see what results you get
看看你会得到什么结果
and when you're done
当你完成后
let's go on to the next video
我们继续下个视频
where we'll talk about one very common
我们将讨论一个非常常见的
use of large language models in software applications
在软件应用程序中使用大型语言模型
which is to summarise text
哪一个是总结文本
so when you're ready let's go on to the next video
当你准备好了，我们继续下一个视频